Man of God, help me!
What happened?
They want to jail me with my children because of a debt.
They want to do what?
To jail me and my children because of the debt that I am owing.
Why?
Money lenders. I borrowed money to start my business, the business collapsed and I could not pay.
They want to jail you?
Yes, man of God, set me free.
What did you use the money for?
I used it to open my business.
How much is the money?
It is 350,000 (naira).
How much do you have?
I don’t have any. Everything scattered.
What do you have in the shop?
Nothing.
I'm selling as if I am not selling. I am not seeing the money.
I am not seeing anything.
I did not use it to buy anything. I could not even use it to feed.
I can't pay my rent. I can't pay my store rent.
Are you living alone?
I am with my children. From Warri (Delta, Nigeria) to this place, I borrowed money to come.
Where is your husband?
Another woman took him from me.
I have been suffering with the children for four years.
OK, it is alright.
Your children, are they schooling?
They are schooling but there is no money to pay their school fees.
What is your problem now? Is it you debt? Or your…
It is the debt, first of all. They want to jail me and my children. Every day, they threaten me.
So, they will jail me with you.
Amen.
Don't worry. It's alright. You will receive your deliverance.
Don't worry, OK?
Your deliverance is more important.
Amen.
OK.
Jesus will pay your money.
Amen.
After paying your money, He will deliver you.
OK, don't cry.
OK?
Yes, sir.
Jesus will help us to pay it.
Amen.
OK, it's alright.
The Lord will use me to deliver her and to pay the debt, which is 350,000 naira.
Praise the Lord!
Hallelujah!
Thank You, Jesus!
People of God, I want you to support now.
This woman must have something to train her children and start business back.
In response to T.B. Joshua's injunction, members begin to come forward to contribute what they have,
in order to support the woman.
Different currencies and denominations were given by the congregation comprising of
both national and international worshippers.
More and more people trooped out to give a worthy offering,
knowing that what they have in their hands now
can be a solution to the problem at hand.
Mrs. Christopher cannot hide her feelings of joy and surprise
as the congregation continues flooding to the offering bowls.
Can you give the woman the 350,000 (naira)?
Look at the screen of your TV. There is a man of God handing over...
giving her the sum of 350,000 naira in cash.
The amount she owes...
This woman must go home with 2 million naira.
Oh, this is how you are!
I used to say that it's a lie, the good things you do.
More and more.
Is it for me?
Sister, is it true? All this is for me?
Watch your screen.
If you must receive, you must learn to give - your love, your kindness.
What we are doing now, we are not doing to display this
but we are communicating to you that this is what the Gospel is all about: care, cheerful giver.
T.B. Joshua gives the lady a hug, as a way of thanking her for even receiving the gift.
The container was then taken to a secure place and counted under the supervision of Mrs. Christopher,
to ensure honesty and transparency.
Now, Mrs. Christopher is going home with more than sufficient funds to pay her debts,
with the assurance that she will receive the remaining donation that the members were still contributing,
which would finally add up to the total of 2 million naira mentioned by T.B. Joshua.
TESTIMONY TIME
My name is Patience Christopher. I am from Ugale South, Delta State, Nigeria.
I am very happy for what the man of God has done in my life today.
I came here wretchedly from Warri, owing debt.
The people I was owing were threatening me and threatening
my children that they were going to jail me and my children.
They even arrested me.
The money that I was owing is 350,000 naira.
When I came to The SCOAN for the first time today, I cried and shouted to the man of God.
The man of God does not know me and I do not know him but as he was passing by,
they showed me the man of God and I cried and called upon him.
Man of God, help me!
What happened?
They want to jail me with my children because of debt.
How much is the money?
It is 350,000 (naira).
He answered me and said that they should give me 350,000 (naira).
Can you give the woman 350,000 (naira)?
Look at the screen of your TV, there is a man of God...
And that the members should contribute.
People of God, I want you to support now.
This woman must have something to train her children and start business back.
After the contribution, I realised 750,000 naira, and
the members are still contributing and I am not a member of this church.
This is my first time of coming to this place. I am very, very surprised for
what God has used them to do for me today.
After receiving 350,000 naira from T.B. Joshua, the members contributed a further 750,000 naira,
and the members are still contributing.
Now, she not only has enough money to pay off her debt, she can restart her business
and care for her family.
Glory be to God.